<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>
<page>
<pageurl>https://job-openings.monster.co.uk/Marketing-Intern-8690-London-UK-Broadgate-Estates/31/c36c7414-7e3a-43bc-8a82-583af4ddba47</pageurl>
<record>
<uniq_id>eb1baf6b11b20f1664dabc660574b5ac</uniq_id>
      <crawl_timestamp>2018-06-22 22:50:37 +0000</crawl_timestamp>
      <url>https://job-openings.monster.co.uk/Marketing-Intern-8690-London-UK-Broadgate-Estates/31/c36c7414-7e3a-43bc-8a82-583af4ddba47</url>
      <job_title>Marketing Intern (8690)</job_title>
      <category>communications</category>
      <company_name>Broadgate Estates</company_name>
      <city>London</city>
      <post_date>2018-05-19</post_date>
      <job_description>At British Land we manage, develop and finance a portfolio of high quality properties. We are a FTSE100 company structured as a Real Estate Investment Trust. Places People Prefer is at the heart of what we do, we create outstanding places that make a positive difference to people’s everyday lives. We are proud of the scale of our portfolio: Nearly 100,000 people live or work in our properties. They are visited around 350 million times each year and over 1,000 different organisations have chosen of our properties as their home. We have £19.1bn assets under management of which we own £13.9bn; our portfolio includes UK retail, Central London offices and prime residential. We have a small head office of around 250 people and outsource many aspects of our business; the size of our team encourages increased responsibility and entrepreneurialism.Role TitleMarketing InternLocationMarble Arch, LondonDivisionMarketingReporting toSenior Marketing Acquisition ManagerOur Offices &amp;amp; Residential portfolio is focused on London, reflecting its position as a leading global city – a place to live, work and do business. We provide a range of working and living space across our campuses atBroadgate,Regent’s PlaceandPaddington Central, as well as at distinctive standalone properties such asThe Leadenhall Building, which all combine a broad mix of retail and leisure.The offices and residential marketing team are responsible for the creation and implementation of the marketing strategy of the London office and residential portfolio. This ranges from taking newly developed buildings to market through to enlivening our campuses with events and activities for our tenants.The RoleA new and exciting position for a university graduate with an interest in a marketing career to join a fast paced FTSE 100 company. The Marketing Intern will provide full support to the Customer Marketing team in the implementation of its marketing strategy.Key ResponsibilitiesUpdating brochure and website contentEnsure all templates and guidelines are in place and complied withWork closely with marketing agencies to ensure implementation of marketing strategyLiaise with all levels within the companyMonthly traffic analysis and dashboard reportsFormatting, sending and creating of HTML (email) newslettersSupport team in physical marketing mail outsSupport team at planning and delivery of launch events and customer eventsEditing and proof reading reports, documents, letters and PowerPoint presentationsPreparing weekly content for internal communicationsWriting briefs and project managementResearch topic per quarter and present back to the team.RequirementsMust have a strong interest to pursue a career in marketingExcellent organisational and communication skillsWorks well under pressure and remains calm at all timesWill be a confident, pro-active, self-starting and highly professional individualMust have advanced knowledge of MS Word, Outlook, PowerPoint and intermediate knowledge of ExcelAbility to prioritise work with competing deadlines in order to respond to the changing internal environmentA proactive approach to improvements; such as suggesting ideas and being open minded to the ideas of othersMust be able to accept and act on feedbackMust have an excellent attention to detail and accuracyMust be able to use own initiativePlease note that we endeavour to get back to all applicants within 28 days. If you haven’t heard from us within this period, please assume that you have been unsuccessful on this occasion.</job_description>
      <company_description> About this company Broadgate Estates </company_description>
      <job_board>monster</job_board>
      <geo>uk</geo>
      <location>NA</location>
</record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://job-openings.monster.co.uk/Corporate-&#x2013;-Risk-Management-&#x2013;-Firmwide-Risk-Reporting-&#x2013;-Country-Risk-&#x2013;-Associate-London-UK-JPMorgan-Chase-Co/31/8e43e17f-01a5-460b-8c54-f7696ee62e33</pageurl>
<record>
<uniq_id>0c4131fc886bab3aa3165a01d608fdda</uniq_id>
      <crawl_timestamp>2018-06-22 23:00:22 +0000</crawl_timestamp>
      <url>https://job-openings.monster.co.uk/Corporate-–-Risk-Management-–-Firmwide-Risk-Reporting-–-Country-Risk-–-Associate-London-UK-JPMorgan-Chase-Co/31/8e43e17f-01a5-460b-8c54-f7696ee62e33</url>
      <job_title>Corporate – Risk Management – Firmwide Risk Reporting – Country Risk – Associate</job_title>
      <category>communications</category>
      <company_name>JPMorgan Chase &amp;amp; Co</company_name>
      <city>London</city>
      <post_date>2018-02-09</post_date>
      <job_description>&amp;lt;div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div align="justify"&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Job Description&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div align="justify"&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div align="justify"&amp;gt;Corporate – Risk Management – Firmwide Risk Reporting – Country – Associate - London&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p align="justify" style="MARGIN-BOTTOM:%200px;%20MARGIN-TOP:%200px"&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div align="justify"&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Description&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p align="justify" style="MARGIN-BOTTOM:%200px;%20MARGIN-TOP:%200px"&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div align="justify"&amp;gt;The global Firmwide Risk Reporting team is responsible for reporting risk exposures across market, credit, country, model and legal entity risk. Risk reports are provided to the Board of Directors, Senior Management and Risk Managers to facilitate a clear understanding and timely management of risk across the firm.&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p align="justify" style="MARGIN-BOTTOM:%200px;%20MARGIN-TOP:%200px"&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Associate Roles and Responsibilities:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p align="justify" style="MARGIN-BOTTOM:%200px;%20MARGIN-TOP:%200px"&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div&amp;gt;This role is part of Country Risk Reporting. There is a heavy analytical nature to this role which requires the ability to have a conceptual conversation with the business and turn that into a high quality end-product with appropriate analytical commentary. The right candidate must understand and challenge the numbers, and be able to tell the story behind them. Additionally, the candidate needs to understand data flows, investigate and remediate data issues between upstream source systems and the Country Risk Infrastructure.&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div&amp;gt;The role entails the collection, aggregation and analysis of data to produce Country Reports which are used by Senior Risk Management to monitor the firm’s overall risk to selected countries. Topics covered within the job profile include derivative, loans and commitments, issuer positions, internal country ratings, new business initiatives, country strategy papers, exposure and stress against Country Limits, and other risk analyses. The right candidate must have an understanding of either market risk or credit risk concepts and must be able to understand and explain complex stress calculations and the theory behind them.&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div align="justify"&amp;gt;The team interacts heavily with the Country Risk Management, Credit Risk Management, various Middle Offices, Credit and Market Risk Reporting, Risk F&amp;amp;BM, Investor Relations and Technology.&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div align="justify"&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div align="justify"&amp;gt;There is a critical need to focus on ensuring that the risk reporting is comprehensive, useable, and accurate so that all levels of risk management can use it to understand and manage the business in a timely and effective manner.&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div align="justify"&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div align="justify"&amp;gt;Specific responsibilities/deliverables include:&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;ol&amp;gt;&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div align="justify"&amp;gt;Contribute to the team’s weekly country reporting to Senior Management&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div align="justify"&amp;gt;Lead the collection, aggregation, and analysis of information related to Country Risk for a particular region. Present findings to Country Risk Management at regular meetings. Provide insight as to the method of stress calculation and factors driving changes to stress levels. Weigh the impact of methodology and process changes and communicate findings to technology and senior management.&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div align="justify"&amp;gt;Crisis Monitoring&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div align="justify"&amp;gt;Assist in ad-hoc data collection and review of information for countries requiring increased scrutiny. Present findings to senior management.&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div align="justify"&amp;gt;Contribute to weekly reports sent to Senior Management and Senior Risk Management&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div align="justify"&amp;gt;Ensure weekly commentary is received and updated, where applicable.&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div align="justify"&amp;gt;Update exposure data and associated comparative commentaries&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div align="justify"&amp;gt;Contribute to the improvement and automation of the Country Risk reporting process&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div align="justify"&amp;gt;Data process automation via Excel and tactical use of Excel macros.&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div align="justify"&amp;gt;Participate in continuing development of new exposure management tool.&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/ol&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p align="justify" style="MARGIN-BOTTOM:%200px;%20MARGIN-TOP:%200px"&amp;gt;&amp;lt;b&amp;gt;Qualifications:&amp;lt;/b&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p align="justify" style="MARGIN-BOTTOM:%200px;%20MARGIN-TOP:%200px"&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div align="justify"&amp;gt;The ideal candidate possesses the following skills:&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div align="justify"&amp;gt;Advanced knowledge of Microsoft Excel and Access, and Business Objects&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div align="justify"&amp;gt;Solid background in the development and use of Macro’s and VBA&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div align="justify"&amp;gt;Strong analytical, quantitative, and problem-solving abilities&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div align="justify"&amp;gt;Product knowledge and / or experience of Wholesale Credit, Market, Country, or Liquidity risk is desirable&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div align="justify"&amp;gt;Good written and verbal communication skills&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div align="justify"&amp;gt;Good team player who can work well with colleagues of various levels, across multiple locations&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div align="justify"&amp;gt;Ability to work under pressure, prioritize multiple tasks, and bring tasks to complete closure&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div align="justify"&amp;gt;Self-motivated and comfortable working with large amounts of data&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div align="justify"&amp;gt;Numerate or IT degree or equivalent desirable&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div align="justify"&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;b&amp;gt;&amp;lt;u&amp;gt;About J.P. Morgan’s Corporate &amp;amp; Investment Bank&amp;lt;/u&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/b&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div&amp;gt;J.P. Morgan’s Corporate &amp;amp; Investment Bank is a global leader across banking, markets and investor services. The world’s most important corporations, governments and institutions entrust us with their business in more than 100 countries. With $18 trillion of assets under custody and $393 billion in deposits, the Corporate &amp;amp; Investment Bank provides strategic advice, raises capital, manages risk and extends liquidity in markets around the world.  Further information about J.P. Morgan is available at&amp;lt;a href="file:///H:/jpmDesk/Desktop/Anaoshak%20Patel/REQ/www.jpmorgan.com" target="_blank"&amp;gt;www.jpmorgan.com&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div&amp;gt;JPMorgan Chase &amp;amp; Co. offers an exceptional benefits program and a highly competitive compensation package. JPMorgan Chase &amp;amp; Co. is an Equal Opportunity Employer.&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;</job_description>
      <company_description> About this company JPMorgan Chase &amp; Co </company_description>
      <job_board>monster</job_board>
      <geo>uk</geo>
      <location>NA</location>
</record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://job-openings.monster.co.uk/Public-Relations-Executive-Manchester-NW-UK-GlobalData/31/91202693-3acb-4875-a596-bc76112570f2</pageurl>
<record>
<uniq_id>7165230abbc7deef03300ca57f581a64</uniq_id>
      <crawl_timestamp>2018-06-22 22:58:29 +0000</crawl_timestamp>
      <url>https://job-openings.monster.co.uk/Public-Relations-Executive-Manchester-NW-UK-GlobalData/31/91202693-3acb-4875-a596-bc76112570f2</url>
      <job_title>Public Relations Executive</job_title>
      <category>communications</category>
      <company_name>GlobalData</company_name>
      <city>Manchester</city>
      <state>NW</state>
      <post_date>2018-06-13</post_date>
      <job_description>GlobalData PLC, a rapidly-expanding international data and analytics company, seeks a talented and versatile candidate to join its global PR team based in its Manchester city centre office. The successful applicant will be primarily responsible for creating/editing compelling press releases to support the company’s PR and marketing function across the healthcare, consumer, technology, retail, and financial services market sectors. To be considered for this role, you must be a confident self-starter who can organise, prioritise and lead the delivery of your workload to meet achievable PR output targets. You should enjoy writing and editing, have an aptitude for identifying key messages and information and the capability to summarise copy content in a PR friendly way. The ideal candidate will have excellent writing and communication skills and the ability to communicate with colleagues at all levels. Liaising with the media, and working with in-house research and analysis teams to develop and launch content marketing campaigns will also be important.Writing, editing and distributing high-quality press releasesWorking closely with GlobalData’s in-house R&amp;A teams to produce effective, targeted press releases that will gain maximum exposure for the companyManaging external-facing content on the company’s website, with a particular attention to maintaining and improving the Media CentreTracking, monitoring and reporting on all activities in regular progress meetings with managementEducated to degree-levelExcellent written and verbal communication skills, with a keen eye for detail and creativityAbility to work as a team and liaise with other internal departments to hit targetsDemonstrable passion to develop a career in PR and social mediaExperience of working in content marketing, PR or the media (desirable, not essential)</job_description>
      <company_description> About this company GlobalData </company_description>
      <job_board>monster</job_board>
      <geo>uk</geo>
      <location>NA</location>
</record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://job-openings.monster.co.uk/ICT-Apprentice-Technician-Liverpool-UK-King-David-Campus/31/c4d5b6e5-2fc6-4a06-8b21-d340aec075d6</pageurl>
<record>
<uniq_id>45fddddc0756ea95b6dd4e80ab43e837</uniq_id>
      <crawl_timestamp>2018-06-22 22:34:14 +0000</crawl_timestamp>
      <url>https://job-openings.monster.co.uk/ICT-Apprentice-Technician-Liverpool-UK-King-David-Campus/31/c4d5b6e5-2fc6-4a06-8b21-d340aec075d6</url>
      <job_title>ICT Apprentice Technician</job_title>
      <category>communications</category>
      <company_name>King David Campus</company_name>
      <city>Liverpool</city>
      <post_date>2018-06-15</post_date>
      <job_description>View Basket        Login      Open MenuICT Apprentice TechnicianJob Title: ICT Apprentice TechnicianEmployer: King David CampusJob Type: Finance &amp;amp; AdministrationJob Phase: Cross PhaseNOR: 697Grade: ApprenticeActual Salary: £182 per weekContract Type: Fixed termContract Term: Full time, Term time onlyLocation: LiverpoolStart Date: Monday, August 13th, 2018Closing Date: Monday, July 2nd, 2018About the SchoolKing David High School is a Jewish faith based school located in South Liverpool and serving the needs of the Jewish and wider community. The last OFSTED Report – June 2010 - judged the school to be outstanding overall and outstanding at Sixth Form.In September 2011 the school moved into state of the art, brand new facilities as part of the King David Campus incorporating King David High School, King David Primary School, King David Kindergarten and community facilities. The school is conveniently located just off the M62.King David High School is an equal opportunities employer and welcomes applications from all sections of society regardless of faith, gender or ethnicity.We are committed to safeguarding and promoting the welfare of children. The posts are subject to enhanced DBS (Disclosure and Barring Service) checks, adherence to Staff Code of Conduct and School Whistleblowing PolicyAbout the RoleAs part of an exciting new phase in development of the campus, governors wish to recruit an in-house ICT team to manage and develop the existing ICT infrastructure and support services.The governors wish to invite applications from suitably qualified individuals with a proven track record to provide an effective ICT support and infrastructure management service to the high school, primary school and kindergarten.Personal QualitiesThe successful candidate will be enthusiastic and highly motivated, eager to make a positive contribution to this thriving campus and will be people who value working as part of a team and ensuring delivery of the highest possible standards.How to ApplyInformation and application forms are available on the school websiteIf you have difficulty accessing our website please contact Jean McMeakin, Office ManagerInterviews will take place from 4th July onwardsClosing Date: Monday 2nd July 2018 at 12pmShort Listing Date: Monday 2nd July 2018Interview Date: Wednesday 4th July 2018Recruitment DocumentsJob Description:Download DocumentPerson Specification:Download DocumentApplication Form:Download DocumentEqual Opportunities Monitoring:Download DocumentContact DetailsKing David CampusChildwall RoadLiverpoolL15 6WUContact Name: Michela IodiceContact Telephone: 0151 235 1420Contact e-mail:[email protected]Website:www.kingdavidliverpool.co.ukNOR: 697 School Improvement LiverpoolToxteth Annexe Conference CentreAigburth Road,Liverpool, L17 7BN0151 233 3901© School Improvement Liverpool Limited 2018Sign up to our newsletterKeep up-to-date with all the latest news and events from School Improvement Liverpool</job_description>
      <company_description> About this company King David Campus </company_description>
      <job_board>monster</job_board>
      <geo>uk</geo>
      <location>NA</location>
</record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://job-openings.monster.co.uk/Marketing-Officer-Grays-HC-UK-thurrock-council/31/75675f45-3db6-4e05-8721-b739c73aaa5b</pageurl>
<record>
<uniq_id>a096056b56355f55b29385c2eb5d4083</uniq_id>
      <crawl_timestamp>2018-06-22 22:35:03 +0000</crawl_timestamp>
      <url>https://job-openings.monster.co.uk/Marketing-Officer-Grays-HC-UK-thurrock-council/31/75675f45-3db6-4e05-8721-b739c73aaa5b</url>
      <job_title>Marketing Officer</job_title>
      <category>communications</category>
      <company_name>thurrock council</company_name>
      <city>Grays</city>
      <state>HC</state>
      <post_date>2017-07-14</post_date>
      <job_description>This is an exciting opportunity to work with both the council’s youth service and corporate communications team, to support the development and implementation of a communications and marketing strategy designed to raise awareness of OnTrack Thurrock. This position is a 6 Month fixed term contract OnTrack is a programme to help young people in Thurrock who are unemployed and not in education or training. We are looking for a communication and marketing professional to support the planning, co-ordinating and implementation of all communications and marketing activity ensuring key messages are consistently applied, using the full range of communication and marketing channels and tools for OnTrack Thurrock. OnTrack Thurrock is part-funded by the European Social Fund and the Youth Employment Initiative to help individuals who are not in employment, education or training. Main Responsibilities and key elements of the role are: To support the development and implementation of a campaign plan for the OnTrack Thurrock Youth Employment Initiative Programme Develop and embed key messages for external audiences and effectively engage with stakeholders To maximise the potential for income generation and sponsorship for OnTrack Thurrock To ensure appropriate co-ordination of activity between services and roles across media, web and design Assist with the creation, development and production of marketing collateral and campaign material Assist with the updating of social media channels Twitter, Facebook and LinkedIn Key Skills and Experience: Ability to plan, deliver and evaluate marketing and communication plans Excellent interpersonal and communication skills Ability to work under pressure, determine priorities and progress a variety of tasks Experience of dealing with the media For an informal discussion about the role, please contact Michele Lucas, Strategic Lead – Learning and Skills or 01375 413674. Our vision – Thurrock: a place of opportunity, enterprise and excellence where individuals, communities and businesses flourish. Thurrock is an exciting place to live and work. We are an emerging cultural and arts centre, home to the production centre for the Royal Opera House and the National Skills Academy for Creative and Cultural Skills . We have retail and leisure that is among the best, with the magnificent intu Lakeside , and breath-taking countryside all around. We are an area of massive growth, which is creating jobs and new industry, but with great transport links that can get you into London and other parts of the UK quickly and easily. Thurrock Council is committed to equal opportunities and welcome applications from all sections of the community. Disabled people will be offered an interview where they meet all essential criteria on the person specification. Job share applications are also welcome. Most departments operate a system of flexible working hours. We serve a diverse community where people are different yet equal. Diversity underpins everything we do. How to Apply Please apply online by clicking Apply. Please note, we do not accept CVs. If you have any difficulties in submitting an application form please email .</job_description>
      <company_description> About this company thurrock council </company_description>
      <job_board>monster</job_board>
      <geo>uk</geo>
      <location>NA</location>
</record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://job-openings.monster.co.uk/Internal-Communications-Co-Ordinator-UK-Direct-Line-Group/31/dc51b949-53f7-4713-b2f7-411b0c40be7d</pageurl>
<record>
<uniq_id>c27b68da238742600156b2e906969c55</uniq_id>
      <crawl_timestamp>2018-06-22 22:34:21 +0000</crawl_timestamp>
      <url>https://job-openings.monster.co.uk/Internal-Communications-Co-Ordinator-UK-Direct-Line-Group/31/dc51b949-53f7-4713-b2f7-411b0c40be7d</url>
      <job_title>Internal Communications Co-Ordinator</job_title>
      <category>communications</category>
      <company_name>Direct Line Group</company_name>
      <post_date>2015-11-06</post_date>
      <job_description>Internal Communications Co-Ordinator Job Number: 17189An exciting new role has arisen within our Internal Communications team for a Co-Ordinator to come on board and join the team. This is a fantastic opportunity for those who are looking for their next step within internal Comms. The role of the Internal Comms Coordinator is to provide support for the Internal Communications team in all aspects of internal and operational comms activity across a number of channelsKey AccountabilitiesContribute to the delivery of the Direct Line Group communications strategy with colleagues to deliver a joined up approach to all communications initiatives.Support the implementation of IC plans for specific audiences, ensuring alignment with key business goals and overall business strategyDeploy a range of IC skills and knowledge to support planning, delivery and measurement of successful internal and operational communications across all channels – online, environmental and face-to-face Monitor and measure internal comms channels including social media, e.g. Yammer providing MI and associated insight to the IC teamEnsure all communications meet the expected high standard of quality in terms of preparation, accuracy, presentation, execution and timelinessMaintain internal relationships with stakeholders using stakeholder management skills Manage external relationships  –designers, AV, printers etc as requiredSupport ad-hoc projects as required ensuring plans are executed to a high standardIdentify, own and manage the risks involved in running our business as appropriate to the role, in line with the company risk frameworkThe ideal candidate will have the following: Minimum 12 Months experience within an Internal Communications roleStrong organisation and admin skillsA real self starter and highly motivated Flexible approach to workGood use of MS OfficeSelection Process Our application process has been designed to make joining us as smooth a transition as possible, it not only provides us with the information we need to decide whether you’re the right person for the job, but also to make sure we’re right for you. Get more details on our application process here. Your Online application No matter which job you’re applying for, completing our online application form is the first thing you need to do. It takes about 10 minutes to complete by uploading your CV and telling us a bit about you.  Take a look at our tips on writing a great CV and before you apply pages to find out what information you’ll need to hand.  Closing date:  Friday 13th November 2015 Career benefits and rewards It all starts with a competitive salary, benchmarked against our competitors, which will grow as you do. We’ve made sure your annual holiday entitlement is attractive too – and what’s more, we let you choose the rewards that suit your lifestyle. That kind of flexibility is a key feature of our benefits package. And there’s plenty to choose from, including: Pension funding of 9% of your base salary – you can choose to contribute less or more than thisIncome protectionLife assurancePrivate medical cover (anyone can choose this through our flexible benefits scheme, and managers receive this as standard)Direct Line Group employees can apply for 50% off Direct Line and Churchill home, motor and pet insurance policiesWe also provide free Direct Line travel insurance and Green Flag breakdown cover to our people.Where can I find out more? You can find out more by speaking to our Recruitment Consultant for this vacancy, Arfana Hussain at arfana.hussain@directlinegroup.co.uk  Please also contact us if you consider yourself to have a disability that requires an adjustment to help facilitate your application, interview or the joining process. Who we are Direct Line Group is an organisation with a clear mission: to make insurance much easier and better value for customers. We're one of the leading motor, home and small business insurers in the UK. We're home to some of the nation's best-known brands, including Direct Line, Churchill, Privilege, Green Flag and NIG.Job: Human ResourcesPrimary Location: BromleyFull-Time/Part-Time: Full-timePosting Date: 05-Nov-2015Contract Type: Fixed Term Contract</job_description>
      <company_description> About this company Direct Line Group </company_description>
      <job_board>monster</job_board>
      <geo>uk</geo>
      <location>NA</location>
</record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://job-openings.monster.co.uk/Public-Sector-Account-Manager-London-London-UK-edenred/31/793c044d-54a9-4bb7-935b-2332e611fe67</pageurl>
<record>
<uniq_id>5b0756675d1eec6aa5f45bd760772409</uniq_id>
      <crawl_timestamp>2018-06-22 22:35:19 +0000</crawl_timestamp>
      <url>https://job-openings.monster.co.uk/Public-Sector-Account-Manager-London-London-UK-edenred/31/793c044d-54a9-4bb7-935b-2332e611fe67</url>
      <job_title>Public Sector Account Manager</job_title>
      <category>communications</category>
      <company_name>edenred</company_name>
      <city>London</city>
      <state>London</state>
      <post_date>2018-06-09</post_date>
      <job_description>Personal Performance: Drive the sales acquisition activity via the CCS framework and coordinate internal resource / support as necessary, including Bids/Tenders, Contracts, Projects, Communications, Client Services, Finance, Product Development, Marketing etc. Manage a portfolio of client relationships implemented under the CCS framework.  Predominantly, these will be the main HM Government Whitehall Depts. Manage other framework relationships, i.e. Health Trust Europe, ESPO, APUC etc. Book review and acquisition meetings nationally as required, introducing additional products and promoting services to drive take-up / engagement to drive volume and revenue growth Team Performance: The PSAM will work alongside the PSSM managing a significant portfolio of existing and prospective clients, providing sales support as necessary. Emphasis of the role is both retention of existing business and portfolio growth through the introduction of additional products / services to new channels and audiences within a client organisation and its divisions. Target Market: Any organisation classified defined as being a public sector body Promotion of public sector frameworks, primarily CCS, through which Edenred products and services are promoted Key Duties: Establish, maintain and execute a comprehensive Public Sector Sales Development Plan, jointly, with the PSAM, the Sales Director and the sales manager, aligned to the overall sales plan / objectives.  The Public Sector Sales Development Plan will consider: Acquisition of key new business targets Framework analysis, mapping Edenred products / services and client use Account management support and activities, aligned to historical and potential volume / revenue; product and service penetration; beneficiary take-up Drive volume and revenues to deliver the sales plan / budget Evolution of CCS framework services as agreed by the Steering Group, generating new volume / revenues Identifying and targeting new Framework’s, ensuring Edenred presence and establishing new, future sales channels Introduce Edenred to other potential framework bodies / organisations, expanding the channels through which Edenred products / services can be delivered 6 month acquisition project – prospect non Edenred clients to join framework with a CCS preference Develop collaborative working relationships and practices with PSSM and wider internal support teams (Operations, Finance, Project Management, IT, Contracts, Communications etc.), engendering spirit of team work and shared ambition. Maintain relationships with key contacts encompassing HR, Commercial, Internal Communications etc. for every client supported by the Public Sector Development Plan. Use client and product / service mapping to identify opportunities to introduce additional Edenred products available via frameworks. Increase audience engagement across all solutions through introduction of marketing / communication plans with clients. Work with Marketing to develop quarterly targeted acquisition campaigns, driving enquiries and sales pipelines across all frameworks Work with Bid &amp; Tender team to complete responses, taking ownership of any bid related to an individual portfolio client, and other client tenders as appropriate those. PSAM is responsible for the final quality checks and approval. Work with the Contracts Manager to ensure the timely and accurate issuing of renewal and new contracts. PSAM assumes commercial ownership to ensure all existing arrangements are managed in accordance with contract requirements Schedule and completion of NPS Questionnaires with key clients in accordance with Customer Satisfaction programme, establishing case and testimonial content Professional handover of accounts as required with documentation and stakeholder mapping Maintain CRM in accordance with company policy; to record important information to enable future commercial relationship development. Understand and provide monthly commentary on public sector performance vs. plan as well as any specific areas of concern / client issues, including provision of monthly board reporting.</job_description>
      <company_description> About this company edenred </company_description>
      <job_board>monster</job_board>
      <geo>uk</geo>
      <location>NA</location>
</record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://job-openings.monster.co.uk/Marketing-Manager-Stamford-MID-UK-skanska/31/c5f910f7-5457-4792-bde3-f1ee7812037e</pageurl>
<record>
<uniq_id>a715e940412d9da17a8e1a25b3e69abf</uniq_id>
      <crawl_timestamp>2018-06-22 22:51:08 +0000</crawl_timestamp>
      <url>https://job-openings.monster.co.uk/Marketing-Manager-Stamford-MID-UK-skanska/31/c5f910f7-5457-4792-bde3-f1ee7812037e</url>
      <job_title>Marketing Manager</job_title>
      <category>communications</category>
      <company_name>skanska</company_name>
      <city>Stamford</city>
      <state>MID</state>
      <post_date>2016-04-20</post_date>
      <job_description>Overview: A multi-focused role aimed at influencing Skanska’s brand in the mission critical market and ultimately increasing sales. This person will have hands on, internal marketing responsibilities and coordinate closely with additional resources on communications and public relations efforts. The right candidate will represent Skanska as a mission critical expert who understands client issues and Skanska differentiators. Core Responsibilities: · Pursuit Participation o Track major national mission critical pursuits via our CRM: SalesForce o Marketing lead or support on major, national pursuits during the strategy, proposal and presentation stages o Develop and drive consistent national messaging in relevant deliverables · Public Relations o Assist in the development and implementation of a national public relations campaign o Research speaking opportunities at national conferences and coordinate all required submissions o Partner with Skanska’s public relations team for article submissions to nationally-focused publications o Create and manage content for external website · S&amp;E COE Information Management o Manage, update and maintain mission critical statistics, boiler, etc. within Cosential o Coordinate, with other COEs, standardized, internal reporting to Skanska leadership o Produce/update miscellaneous marketing materials including brochures, executive summaries, etc. o Produce project case studies by interviewing project team members to capture and share details on significant projects o Capture A/E and competitor intelligence and work towards developing a communication system to distribute and share as appropriate o Research projects (client intelligence, reports on mission critical experience, etc.) o Field marketing requests o Track wins/losses o Create schedules for marketing initiatives/campaigns o Create and distribute internal communication pieces · National conferences, seminars and meetings o Identify appropriate sponsorship programs o Coordinate logistics and execution plans for tradeshow exhibits o Represent Skanska at pertinent tradeshows and conferences o Plan and implement internal and/or external education webinars o Plan, implement and execute client events Skills: Writing/communication skills; experience with InDesign and databases; hands-on experience producing proposals/presentations; professional yet charismatic personality Position does require some travel. Skanska USA is one of the largest, most financially sound construction and development companies in the U.S., serving a broad range of clients including those in transportation, power, industrial, water/wastewater, healthcare, education, sports, data centers, government, aviation and commercial. Headquartered in New York with offices in 31 metro areas, we have more than 11,000 employees committed to being leaders in safety, project execution, sustainability, ethics and people development. In 2015, our work in building construction, civil and power/industrial construction, commercial development and infrastructure development (public-private partnerships) generated $7.1 billion in revenue. Global revenue of parent company Skanska AB, headquartered in Stockholm and listed on the Stockholm Stock Exchange, totaled $18.4 billion in 2015. Skanska shares are publicly traded in the U.S. on the OTC market under the symbol SKBSY through a Level I American Depository Receipt program.     Primary Location US-Connecticut US-CT-Plainville, US-ME-Sanford, US-NJ-Parsippany, US-NJ-Boonton, US-NJ-Atlantic Highlands, US-CT-Stamford, US-ME-Portland, US-NY-Elmsford, US-NJ-Atlantic City, US-CO-Golden, US-CT-Middletown, US-MD-Bowie, US-CT-New Haven, US-CT-Branford, US-CT-Newington, US-CT-Waterbury, US-District of Columbia, US-CT-Hartford, US-NJ-Camden, US-NJ-Basking Ridge, US-CT-New London, US-Delaware, US-NY-Garden City, US-DC-Washington, US-CO-Glenwood Springs, US-NJ-Bergenfield, US-NY-Brooklyn, US-Massachusetts</job_description>
      <company_description> About this company skanska </company_description>
      <job_board>monster</job_board>
      <geo>uk</geo>
      <location>NA</location>
</record>
</page>
<page>
<pageurl>https://job-openings.monster.co.uk/Associate-Director-Employee-Engagement-London-UK-Edelman/31/c8d1e231-bf91-4926-a6b9-71c36a586bbe</pageurl>
<record>
<uniq_id>66b792cdf549f99f62f36303875e1a48</uniq_id>
      <crawl_timestamp>2018-06-22 22:59:41 +0000</crawl_timestamp>
      <url>https://job-openings.monster.co.uk/Associate-Director-Employee-Engagement-London-UK-Edelman/31/c8d1e231-bf91-4926-a6b9-71c36a586bbe</url>
      <job_title>Associate Director - Employee Engagement</job_title>
      <category>communications</category>
      <company_name>Edelman</company_name>
      <city>London</city>
      <post_date>2018-05-16</post_date>
      <job_description>Associate Director - Employee EngagementOrganization: EdelmanPractice Area: CorporateDescriptionEdelman is the world’s largest communications marketing agency with 5,500+ professionals across 65 offices worldwide. Since it was founded in 1952 it remains independent and family- owned. The London office boasts more than 550 people with specialist practices including consumer brand, research, corporate reputation, public affairs, healthcare and technology. We have been named in The Sunday Times 100 Best Companies to Work For, for the last seven years in a row, and have been awarded 13 Cannes Lions including the Grand Prix for PR in 2014. This year we won The Global Agency of The Year award at the Sabre Awards (2016). Our previous accolades include; Pan-EMEA Consultancy of the Year (Sabre Awards 2015), PR Week Large Agency of the Year (2011) in both the US and UK and International Consultancy of the Year (PRCA Awards 2013)London’s Corporate Reputation team includes more than 80 consultants. The team includes former journalists, senior in-house practitioners, government advisors and industry specialists as well as dedicated media, crisis and employee engagement experts, who develop and deliver integrated communications strategies and programmes for some of the world’s leading brands. Our Employee Engagement team develops and executes engagement strategies that influence the employee behaviours that drive business results. The Role We are looking for an Account Director/Associate Director to help grow Edelman’s Employee Engagement practice. Our expertise includes: •Creating and telling a consistent, inclusive story that employees understand, support and feel proud to share with others •Developing change programmes that help leaders and managers engage their teams with authenticity, credibility and consistency •Design and execution of Employee Value Proposition/Employer Branding programmes •Deploying collaboration tools that help employees share ideas and learn from each other •Identifying the right communication channels and design to ensure messages reach employees in the most effective, appropriate and timely way •Leading change and culture communications including vision, values and purpose •Managing large-scale change and transaction support often caused by restructuring, mergers, acquisitions or divestitures The successful candidate will work closely with Edelman’s UK Employee Engagement lead and the wider team. They will help to develop the business by supporting on sales and marketing activity, managing client projects, liaising with clients on a day-to-day basis and delivering outstanding employee communications project work. Qualification:Key Requirements: •Proven track record in employee engagement or internal communications with large organisations •Clear understanding of the importance of employee engagement for driving business success, and how employee engagement fits with other stakeholder engagement techniques •Familiarity and experience with all aspects of employee engagement programming including appropriate use of communication channels and media, particularly digital media •Highly adaptable and able to work across several clients and projects, managing them all confidently and with a high level of competence •Experience of managing clients – either at an agency or in-house as a communications/engagement business partner •Excellent planning, organisational and programme management skills, particularly relating to the development and ongoing management of employee engagement programmes About Edelman:Edelman is a leading global communications marketing firm that partners with many of the world’s largest and emerging businesses and organizations, helping them evolve, promote and protect their brands and reputations. Edelman was awarded the Grand Prix Cannes Lion for PR in 2014; six Cannes Lions in 2015; and the Grand Prix in the Titanium category in 2016. The firm was named “2016 Global Agency of the Year” by the Holmes Report, and one of Advertising Age’s “Agencies to Watch” in 2014. In 2015, Edelman was among Glassdoor’s “Best Places to Work” for the fifth time. Edelman owns specialty firms Edelman Intelligence (research) and United Entertainment Group (entertainment, sports, experiential), a joint venture with United Talent Agency. Visit http://www.edelman.com for more information.Job: Client Services - CorporatePrimary Location: United Kingdom-LondonJob Type: ExperiencedSchedule: Full-timeJob Posting: May 15, 2018, 11:06:33 AM</job_description>
      <company_description> About this company Edelman </company_description>
      <job_board>monster</job_board>
      <geo>uk</geo>
      <location>NA</location>
</record>
</page>
</root>
